http://www.micromass.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - MicroMass Communications, Inc.
Why Behavioral Science?
Join Us
Thank you for your interest.
Fill out the form, and we’ll be in touch.
Please leave this field empty.
We have successfully received your message.
Thank You
Privacy Policy
EFFECTIVE DATE: November 16, 2017
MicroMass Communications, Inc., recognizes that the privacy of information is important. As a result, this privacy statement provides an overview of the information collected via micromass.com (and other web properties) and how that information may be used.
This policy covers all data that is shared by a visitor with us whether directly via www.micromass.com or via email.
This policy provides an explanation as to what happens to any personal data that you share with us or that we collect from you either directly via this Website or via email.
Certain businesses are required under the Data Protection Act to have a data controller. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 our data controller is Kai Taylor, who can be reached at mmc.privacy@micromass.com.
1. Information we collect
In operating our Website we may collect and process the following data about you:
We collect anonymous, aggregate information regarding visits to micromass.com (IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other non–personally identifiable information) to analyze trends for ongoing site improvement. We use web-tracking software to analyze traffic to this Website to understand our customers’ and visitors’ needs and to continually improve the Website. This web-tracking software will collect only anonymous, aggregate statistics.
Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website, such as when you register to receive information such as a newsletter or contact us via the Contact Us page.
Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.
2. Use of cookies
On occasion, we may gather information about your computer for our services, and to provide statistical information regarding the use of our Website to our advertisers.
Such information will not identify you personally; it is statistical data about our visitors and their use of our site. This statistical data does not identify any personal details whatsoever. It is used by us to analyze how visitors interact with the Website so that we can continue to develop and improve this Website.
We may gather information about your general Internet use by using a cookie file that is downloaded to your computer. Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically.
This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer as cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our Website.
All computers have the ability to decline cookies. This can be done by activating the setting on your browser which enables you to decline the cookies. Please note that should you choose to decline cookies, you may be unable to access particular areas of our Website.
3. Use of your information
Certain activities on the website may require you to provide personal information. Personal information (name, email address, phone number, mailing address) is collected on a voluntary basis in response to a question, comment, or inquiry and may be used for ongoing communications regarding MicroMass Communications, Inc., and its offerings.
We do not sell, trade, or share any personal information to third parties unless otherwise disclosed at the time of collection.
We have deployed physical, electronic, technological, and administrative controls to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure appropriate use of information. Please note that even with these safeguards, data transmission over the Internet is not 100 percent secure.
All resumes and cover letters received will be treated in a confidential manner.
By using our site, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and storage of information as described in this privacy policy. This privacy policy may be amended from time to time. Any changes to this policy will be posted to this Privacy Policy page. If you have questions or concerns about a privacy-related issue, please email us at mmc.privacy@micromass.com.
View our security and privacy statement for the programs we develop for our clients.
4. Disclosing your information
Where applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company, and its other subsidiaries.
We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:
Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.
Where we are legally required to disclose your information.
5. Third party links
Our website may contain links to and from other websites not maintained by MicroMass Communications, Inc. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other such Websites.
6. Social media audiences
We use Facebook Custom Audiences to deliver advertisements to Website Visitors on Facebook based on email addresses that we have collected.
Learn more about Facebook Custom Audiences.
If you want more information about opting out of advertisements from MicroMass, visit the “Access to information” below. We also may use information associated with Visitor social media accounts, such as demographic and other information about an individual’s title, industry, or organization, to improve our marketing efforts if that individual connects those social media accounts to a Website profile.
7. Access to information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at mmc.privacy@micromass.com or by phone at 919.851.3182.
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
8. Contacting us
We welcome any queries, comments, or requests you may have regarding this policy please do not hesitate to contact us at mmc.privacy@micromass.com.
If you would prefer to write to us, our contact address is:
MicroMass Communications, Inc.
MICROMASS COMMUNICATIONS, INC.
100 Regency Forest Dr.Suite 400, Cary, NC 27518
919.851.3182
Get in touch
Behavioral Science
Why Behavioral Science?
We Are MicroMass. We Are Specialists.
Privacy Policy
Security & Privacy
Sitemap
©2020 MicroMass Communications, Inc. All rights reserved.
Thank you for your interest.
Fill out the form, and we’ll be in touch.
Please leave this field empty.
We have successfully received your message.
Thank You
